Okay, so I asked you to search for textview android.
我想要你搜尋textview android
Usually, when I do a search, I always add the word android at the end of it,
一般情況下 在我進憲搜尋時 我會在后面加上android字樣
so that it only shows me android results.
這樣就只會顯示 android結果
The first link is for TextView, and it's on developer.android.com site so
每一個連結是關於TextView的 位於developer.android.com上
I'm going to click on it.
因此我需要按一下它
I can ignore most of the information on this page except
我可以忽略這個頁面上的 大多數資訊
I do want to verify that this is indeed for TextView.
但是我需要確定 它是關於TextView的
I can read the class overview but the most important thing is down here,
我可以閱讀類別概覽 最重要的內容在這裏
the XML attributes.
也就是XML屬性
So I can manually scroll the list, but that will literally take forever.
我可以手工卷動這個清單 但是這個清單實在太長了
So, I'm going to use the fine feature that I talked about earlier.
因此我要使用前面講過的 細化篩選功能
The quiz question was about finding an attribute that would change the text to
測驗題的內容是讓我們找到 相關的屬性 以便將文字更改為
be bold or italic.
粗體或斜體
So I'm going to search for the word bold.
因此我們搜尋 bold字樣
Cool, so let's look at this description.
很好 讓我們來看這段描述
It says Style (bold, italic, bolditalic) for the text.
它介紹文字的樣式 （粗體 斜體 粗斜體）
That sounds pretty good, so I can click on this attribute.
看上去不錯 我按一下這個屬性
For android:textStyle, it seems that the different values are normal, bold,
對於android:textStyle 不同的設定值包括 normal bold
or italic.
或 italic
Let's try it out.
讓我們來嘗試一下
The documentation says that if I add android:textStyle attribute,
文檔告訴我們 如果我 新增android:textStyle屬性
then I can set it to be bold, italic, or normal.
我可以把它設定為bold italic或normal
So let's try bold.
讓我們來嘗試bold屬性
Nice, and it bolds the font.
很好 字體變粗了
And let's be adventurous and try italic as well.
現在讓我們來嘗試italic屬性
Awesome, it italicizes the text.
很好 文字變成斜體了
So this was an example of how you can look at documentation
這個例子告訴我們 你可以查閱文檔
to find new attributes that you can set on your TextView.
搜尋新的屬性 然後在TextView上設定這些屬性
In the future, when you're working on something and you get stuck, or
以後 如果你 遇到問題
you don't know how to do it,
而不知道應該怎麼做
remember they can always use documentation as a resource.
你可以查閱文檔 來幫解你解決問題